Although when he's in Batman pajamas...
(Bernadette:)...sometimes it feels like
I'm touching his inner child.
(Amy:)It's probably because they were bullied.
In a world where you can't fight back...
(Amy:)...superheroes provide
meaningful wish-fulfillment.
Hmm. Now I feel bad for picking on
all those kids.
Although if Danny Biffle
didn't want to eat a mouthful of dirt...
(Penny:)...he shouldn't have shown up
to school wearing a bow tie.
(Bernadette:)I've never even read a comic book.
You guys?
(Penny:)Mm-mm.
- No.
(Bernadette:)It's such an important part of their lives.
(Bernadette:)- Maybe we should try reading some.
- Seriously?
(Bernadette:)The comic book store isn't far from here.
(Penny:)That is an amazing idea.
(Penny:)Okay, how many of these have I had?
(Sheldon:)I think you should turn on the GPS.
(Leonard:)It is on.
(Sheldon:)But the turn-by-turn voice option isn't on.
(Sheldon:)I know I'd feel more safe
if you turn on the turn-by-turn voice option.